https://www.capuchinfriars.org.au/privacy/

PRIVACY POLICYWhat information do we collect?We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form.When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.What do we use your information for?Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:To personalise your experience
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)To improve our website
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)To improve customer service
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)To process transactions
(Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.)To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other website feature relating to RedOne Australia.To send periodic emails
(The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.)How do we protect your information?We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.Do we use cookies?Yes, Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognise your browser and capture and remember certain information, in order to make your experience more pleasant.Do we disclose any information to outside parties?We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or other’s rights, property, or safety.Third party linksOccasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.Your ConsentBy using our site, you consent to our websites Privacy Policy and Terms & Conditions.Changes to our Privacy PolicyIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below.This policy was last modified on 31/08/2017Contacting UsIf there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us by using the contact details below.www.capuchinfriars.org.auCapuchin Mission Office
96 Catherine Street,
Leichhardt NSW 2040
Australia.Phone:  (02) 9569 1880
Email:  mission@capuchinfriars.org.au
Search for:
Search
My Shopping CartProduct CategoriesSeraphic Mass EnrolmentCards & CalendarsBooksCD'sDVD'sReligious ItemsDonations
